{
  "data": {
    "title": "Score on Element: Community Development",
    "description": "This element measures companies disclosures, policies and knowledge systems on its role in fostering community development by addressing local priorities and respecting local concerns and knowledge.",
    "name": "BHARAT HEAVY ELECTRICALS LTD",
    "brand_name": "India Responsible Business Forum",
    "data_point": 66,
    "has_brand_logo":true,
    "growth_fall_summary": "No change as compared to last year",
    "sub_questions": [
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain policy and/ or detailed mechanisms on identifying thrust areas for community development projects?",
        "answer": "Yes, detailed mechanisms"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain policy and/ or detailed mechanisms on identifying backward regions for implementing community development projects?",
        "answer": "Yes, mechanisms"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain policy and/ or detailed mechanisms on identifying target stakeholders and communities with whom they plan to impelemnt their community development projects? Does it specifically mention women, SC/ ST, PwD and children?",
        "answer": "Yes, specifically mentions women, SC, ST, PWD and Children"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain knowledge systems on consultation with stakeholders (community, women, elderly, children) for the formulation of Corporate Social Responsibility policy?",
        "answer": "No"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain whether it has carried out the needs assessment for initiating CSR project?",
        "answer": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain whether the needs assessment for initiating CSR project involved vulnerable groups?",
        "answer": "No"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain policy and/ or detailed mechanisms for implementing CSR projects?",
        "answer": "Yes, mechanisms"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain its contribution for CSR projects as % of profits?",
        "answer": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain the number of beneficiaries of its CSR projects?",
        "answer": "No"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain the distribution of its expenses on CSR projects across themes?",
        "answer": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain details of the projects implemented under CSR?",
        "answer": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain steps taken to ensure that community development initiative is successfully adopted by the community?",
        "answer": "No"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain policy and/ or detailed mechanisms for monitoring CSR projects?",
        "answer": "Yes, mechanisms"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain whether it has carried out any independent impact assessment of its CSR  projects?",
        "answer": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain whether the independent impact assessment of its CSR  projects involve stakeholders like women, children, PwD, SC, ST and elderly?",
        "answer": "No"
      },
      {
        "question": "Has disclosed in public domain the frequency of CSR committee meetings?",
        "answer": "Yes"
      }
    ],
    "current_score": [
      {
        "year": 2015,
        "value": 0.514285714285714
      },
      {
        "year": 2016,
        "value": 0.657142857142857
      },
      {
        "year": 2017,
        "value": 0.657142857142857
      }
    ],
    "average_score": [
      {
        "year": 2015,
        "value": 0.484054834054834
      },
      {
        "year": 2016,
        "value": 0.56260162601626
      },
      {
        "year": 2017,
        "value": 0.59519906323185
      }
    ]
  }
}